<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Raconteur Sound]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Raconteur Sound]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/raconteur-sound/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 22:05:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/raconteur-sound/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colin Lechner]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Colin Lechner</h1><p>Colin Lechner is a talented storyteller, using sound to enhance narrative productions. He holds a Masters of Fine Arts in Sound Design from Savannah College of Art and Design, where he was an integral fixture of the Sound Design Department graduating at the top of his class as the Presidential Medalist (SCAD Presidential Medalist Video). He has served as a sound engineer, mixer, and sound designer on numerous projects spanning a variety of genres including: narrative feature film, web series, narrative live action short, animation short, and documentary.Born in Colorado, Colin performed professionally as a mandolinist with Carin Mari & Pony Express. During this time, he began to explore the technical side of audio production, performing front of house mixing and spearheading the engineering and mixing of many of the group's album releases. Colin also holds a BA in Theatre Arts from Colorado Mesa University, with a concentration in Sound Design. As an undergraduate, he taught theatre and film sound courses at Mesa State College and Western Colorado Community College. Colin is currently developing a second companion sound effects library to the original Colinized Sculpture Library, which features the sounds of a custom designed steel sound sculpture.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/raconteur-sound/colin-lechner/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ad71b767-5c0c-47e6-8051-81671cb953d9</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 22:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Home]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Home</h1><p>Stories are told time and time again. A raconteur makes you feel like you’re hearing it for the first time. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/raconteur-sound/stories-are-told-time-and-time-again-a-raconteur-makes-you/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">13c7f041-70cc-42ed-b5c6-a03f069f0718</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 21:53:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>